<package>
	<id>net.limneos.nfcwriterx</id>
	<name>NFCWriter XS</name>
	<version>3.2-16</version>
	<compatibility>
		<firmware>
			<miniOS>10.0</miniOS>
		</firmware>
	</compatibility>
	<dependencies>
		<package>mobilesubstrate</package>
	</dependencies>
	<shortDescription>NFCWriter XS for iOS 11/12/13 cracked by PotatsoEXP</shortDescription>
	<descriptionlist>
		<description><![CDATA[
<strong>Scan. Write. Copy. Format. Emulate. Serve.</strong><br>
<br>
<strong>Scan your NFC tags, Credit/Debit Cards, MRTD Documents (passports, ID Cards) on your iPhone!</strong><br>
<br>
- Use your iPhone's NFC Chip to its maximum!<br>
<br>
As pre-seen in <a target="_blank" href="https://9to5mac.com/2017/05/19/developer-hacks-nfc-iphone-6s-respond-nfc-devices/">9to5mac</a><br>
<br>
<strong>Features:</strong><br>
<br>
-<strong>Read</strong> most common tag types<br>
<br>
-<strong>Write</strong> tags<br>
<br>
-<strong>Copy</strong> tags<br>
<br>
-<strong>Copy to multiple</strong> tags<br>
<br>
-<strong>Format</strong> tags<br>
<br>
-<strong>Read/Write NDEF</strong> messages<br>
<br>
-<strong>Read/Write</strong> almost all types of tags<br>
<br>
-<strong>Read Full Memory</strong> of  tags<br>
<br>
-<strong>Emulate Tags</strong> with UID <strong>and NDEF message</strong> emulation! (ISO-DEP Protocol) <br>
<br>
-<strong>Manage</strong> and save your tags in one place.<br>
<br>
-<strong>Scan Tags in the background!</strong> (With App minimized or phone locked)<br>
<br>
-<strong>Perform actions</strong> based on your tag's contents.<br>
<br>
-<strong>Display information</strong> about your tags like Manufacturer, Tag Type, Serial Number, ATQA, SAK, Memory Size etc.<br>
<br>
<strong><span style="font-size:20">And for the first time ever:</span></strong><br>
<br>
-<strong>Read EMV Cards</strong> (Credit/Debit Cards, Visa, MasterCard, AMEX, Maestro etc)<br>
<br>
-<strong>Read MRTD documents</strong> (Passports, ID Cards, Driver Licenses that contain an NFC chip)<br>
<br>
-<strong>Serve a tag from an iPhone to a remote iPhone and emulate it remotely!</strong> (Even in background)<br>
<br>
-<strong>Send commands manually to  tags (Advanced Users)</strong><br>
<br>
-<strong>Assign Activator actions to be performed when a specific tag is detected in background</strong><br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
Some notes on the release:<br>
<br>
- NFCWriter (and iOS devices in general) will NOT detect low-frequency RFID tags. You can only use this application with High-Frequency NFC tags (13.56MHz). <a href="https://blog.atlasrfidstore.com/rfid-vs-nfc" target="_blank">Read here for more info</a><br>
<br>
- While it can read and write most NFC tags, Emulation mode with NDEF message will only work for ISO-DEP and Desfire type tags. For different type of tags, like Mifare, NTAG or other tag types, you can only emulate their UID.<br>
<br>
- In NDEF Emulation mode, the emulator accepts also to write NDEF messages to it. This may be useful in applications where you emulate a message, the reader reads it, updates it and reads it back to verify its contents.<br>
<br>
- Emulation can emulate the tag's UID and include NDEF messages. It cannot emulate the whole tag's memory or encrypted info, so if you're trying to emulate a security tag, like door-opening tags, it may or may not work depending on the tag's infrastructure and its built-in security.<br>
<br>
- <strong>However, serving a tag remotely (Server - Client option, ISO-DEP only)</strong> can transfer all the tag's data, including it's security contents, to the remote device. So, for example, you could leave your bus card at home (needs a second iPhone) and emulate it with your main iPhone remotely while in the bus. (May require opening ports to your router)<br>
<br>
<br>
- These achievements are beyond just accessing Apple's own NFC frameworks.<br>
There has been extensive research and this app manages directly the NFC chip on a driver level.<br>
<br>
<br>
-Supported tag types are ISO 14443, Mifare, ISO 15693, ISO-DEP and more.<br>
<br>
-Supported protocols are ISO 14443, ISO-DEP and Mifare.<br>
<br>
This new achievement enables you to use the NFC chip beyond iOS's limitations.<br>
<br>
Research for more Tag types and protocols is constant.<br>
<br>
This is the first time that NFC chip on iPhone is used to this extent.<br>
<br>
Supported Devices: iPhone 6S and up.<br>
iOS : 10 to 13<br>
<br>
Check the screenshots and...<br>
Enjoy!
		]]>
		</description>
	</descriptionlist>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot>
			<description>This is a description for screenshot 1. It's Cydia!</description>
			<image>cydia.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>		
		<screenshot>
			<description>This is a description for screenshot 2. It's another Cydia!</description>
			<image>cydia.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>		
	</screenshots>
	<changelog>
		<change>cracked Ver. release</change>
	</changelog>
	<links>
		<link>
			<name>/r/jailbreak</name>
			<url>https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak</url>
			<iconclass>fa fa-reddit</iconclass>
		</link>
	</links>
</package>
